totousa.com 2019-03-22

# Privacy Policy - TotoUSA.com

PRIVACY POLICY   
Effective Date: August 1, 2018

TOTO USA is a United States subsidiary of TOTO, LTD. operating solely within the Americas.  TOTO USA respects the privacy of users who visit this Site. This Privacy policy applies to the totousa.com website (“Site”), owned and operated by Toto USA, Inc. By using the Site and submitting information you agree that we may use and disclose your information according to the terms of this Policy.

The use of your information is subject to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions in effect at the time of use. Please read our Privacy Policy from time to time, since we may modify it at any time at our sole discretion. If we make material substantive changes, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on our Site with a new Effective Date. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties or the content of linked sites although we do encourage you to read the applicable privacy policies and terms and conditions of such parties or web sites

## Data Processing and Cross-Border Data Transfers

Our Site intended for use by visitors from the Americas.  We offer translations of our Site into French or Spanish for our visitors from Canada and Central and South America.  The Site is maintained on servers located in the United States, and personal information submitted is stored on our servers in the United States.

The TOTO Store is available for purchases shipped only into the continental United States.  Purchases from outside that territory are not permitted. If you are visiting our Site from outside the United States, please be advised that your information is transferred to our U.S. servers.  Please navigate to the Global tab on the Site to locate the TOTO website serving your location.

Disclosing your personal information to us pursuant to this Privacy Policy is at your own risk.  By allowing us to collect information about you, all users, including without limitation users in Canada and the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, such transfer and processing of your data as described in this Privacy Policy. We strive to comply with laws of jurisdictions in which we maintain operations but we make no representations that the practices described in this Privacy Policy are compliant with laws outside those jurisdictions that apply to the collection, security, use and disclosure of personal information.

## Keeping Your Information Secure

We have implemented and maintain reasonable physical, administrative and technical methods to protect your information. You also play a role in protecting your information. You can help to maintain the security of your online transactions by not sharing your account logon or password with anyone and by changing your password regularly.

## Information We Collect and How We Use It

Information You Provide. When you register with TOTO USA, for instance to make a purchase, we collect profile information from you through our registration form. This may include your name, address, e-mail address, shipping address, and telephone number. Providing personal information is solely your choice. However, certain services may not be fully available to you if requested information is not provided. We may also ask you to select a user name and password or identification number to gain access to certain portions of our Site. We may also ask you to provide optional demographic information such as, but not limited to, your zip code, your age range, your business, or your product preferences. When you register for any TOTO USA services, your user name and password are recorded for the purpose of maintaining your own accounts within the Site. Our servers also record e-mail addresses that you submit for registration. If you access our Site through a Social Media account we may also receive information about you, your digital identity, or your contacts from your social media account depending on how you have set your preferences on such account.

Communications with Us.  If you choose to communicate with us, whether by email, telephone, postal mail or by using our online chat feature, we will collect and store the information you provide.

Our Site may allow residents of the United States to purchase certain products through our TOTO Store, an independent website which we own and operate. When you place an order we will require that you provide your contact information including address, email address and telephone number, your payment card information and associated billing address and telephone number, and your shipping address. Information about your payment is protected during transmission to us using industry standard technology.

If you would like to e-mail a page or pages from our Site to a friend, we will collect the recipient’s e-mail address for purposes of that transmission. However, we may not maintain a permanent record of that address unless the recipient independently registers with TOTO USA.

We may use the information we collect from you for our legitimate operational and development interests, for example:

  * to respond to your requests or inquiries,
  * to process transactions you have requested,
  * to manage or facilitate the operation and security of the Site,
  * to enhance your experience with TOTO USA,
  * to communicate with you about transactions or registration, and about products, services, events and other opportunities related to TOTO USA,
  * to identify you or authenticate your identity,
  * to communicate with you regarding your account with us,
  * to monitor and improve the use and satisfaction of Site users,
  * to display advertisements relevant to your interests,
  * to conduct research and analysis and
  * to expand our services and outreach within the United States.

Automatically Collected Information. When a visitor requests pages on the TOTO USA site, our servers automatically recognize the browser’s domain name and IP address. We may also collect statistical information about how visitors are generally searching or using the Site and reserve the right to compile and publish profile information about our visitors without the visitor’s name and addresses for reasonable business purposes.

We do not use technology that recognizes a “do-not-track” signal from your web browser.

Cookies. We may use “cookies” (small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive) to track sessions and to personalize your experience on our Site so that we may improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users’ needs. You can adjust your browser setting to limit or refuse cookies. If you refuse cookies, this will limit system performance and may even cause certain features of the Site to malfunction or not to work at all. Further general information about cookies and how they work is available at www.allaboutcookies.org. The cookies we use on our Site include:

Session Cookies: These temporary cookies expire and are automatically erased whenever you close your browser window. We use session cookies to grant our users access to content and to enable actions they must be logged in to do.

Persistent Cookies: These usually have an expiration date in the distant future and remain in your browser until they expire or you manually delete them. We use persistent cookies to better understand usage patterns so we can improve the site for our customers. For example, we may use a persistent cookie to associate you with your user account or to remember that your choices on the Site, but this only works when cookies on our site are enabled.

Third Party Cookies: We permit limited third parties to place cookies through the Site to provide us with better insights into the use of the Site or user demographics or to provide relevant advertising to you. These third parties may collect information about a consumer’s online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our website. For example, we utilize an analytics program to analyze usage patterns of the Site. We do not control the use of such third party cookies or the resulting information and we are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

## Your Choices.

We may use your email address to contact you to respond to your inquiries, to send you newsletters or announcements, to invite you to participate in surveys, or to provide information about products or services to you. You can elect not to receive promotional emails from us by unsubscribing using the mechanism provided in an email you receive from us.

## How TOTO USA Shares Your Information.

In general, TOTO USA will not share your information with anyone who is not an employee or affiliate of TOTO USA, or who has not signed an appropriate non-disclosure agreement. TOTO USA may disclose personally identifiable information about you to any unaffiliated third party : (1) if you request or authorize it; (2) if the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; (3) if the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) if the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); (5) if the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); (6) to allow them to market to you, or (7) as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-Personal Information, such as usage statistics of our Products, to our affiliates and third parties.

## Keeping Information Accurate

If you ever find that your account information is not complete, not accurate or not current, please e-mail, call or write to us as noted below. We will correct any erroneous information as quickly as possible. You may amend your personal profile at any time by clicking on the “My TOTO” link on any page.

## TOTO USA and Children

TOTO USA’s business and website are not designated to be attractive to children. We do not knowingly collect data from children, and we do not knowingly market to children. Our terms and conditions of use require that any registration may only be made by those over the age of 18. If we have reason to believe that information is being provided by a child under the age of 18 TOTO USA will not collect the information without parental consent or parental notification, which will include the opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information or to prevent the child’s participation in the activity. If a child has provided us with personal information, a parent or guardian of that child should contact TOTO USA customer service and request that information be removed. Without parental consent, online information will only be used to respond to an unsolicited request and for no other purposes. We recognize that protecting children’s identities and privacy online is important and that the responsibility to do so rests with both the online industry and with parents.

## Your California Privacy Rights

For California Residents Only. We may disclose your personal information to our affiliates or other third parties including who may use that information to market to you directly. Pursuant to California’s “Shine the Light Act”, California residents are permitted to request information about the manner in which we share certain categories of information with third parties for their marketing use. Please email us at california to request a copy of our disclosure pursuant to California law.

[Alternative- offer opt out of sharing PII for marketing use: We may disclose your personal information to our affiliates or third parties who may use that information to market directly to you. You have the option to tell us not to share your information. To opt-out please [describe process]. We will not share your information after we have received your notification that you are opting out.]

## How to Contact Us

This site is owned and operated by TOTO USA, Inc. If you have any questions or suggestions with respect to this policy, or if you wish to ask us to delete, correct, or show you your information as provided above, please contact us at webinfo@totousa.com by e-mail, by telephone at 770-282-8686, or by mail at:

 **TOTO USA**  
Attn: Website Manager   
1155 Southern Road   
Morrow, GA 30260  
Choices and Opting Out.
